Muhammad Rizky Haksono

Malang, Indonesia 65152 • mrizkyhaksono@gmail.com • +628973889299

SUMMARY

Experience in Software Development with skills in Web and Mobile Development. Strong problem-solving abilities and a proactive approach to system enhancements and upgrades. Fluent in English and native in Bahasa Indonesia, with effective communication and instructional skills. I am still an undergraduate and have experience related to web and mobile development as well as UI/UX design.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY MUHAMMADIYAH MALANG

Bachelor of Computer Science (GPA 3.90/4.00)

Malang, East Java, Indonesia September 2021 - Present

EXPERIENCES

INFORMATICS LABORATORY UMM - PART TIME

Malang, East Java, Indonesia August 2022 - Present

Information Systems

- Instructed informatics courses and supported lab system management curriculum.
- Participating in documentation Sevenman with XWiki.
- Contributed to Re-engineering Sevenman using Next.js as a project manager and frontend.
- Contributed to Re-engineering Jacket Lab using Laravel Inertia and documentation on user guide.
- Contributed to <u>Re-engineering iLab</u> frontend using Next.js, Material UI, and Redux Toolkit on retaker, faq, and log page.
- Contributed to <u>Sirenta</u> to maintain admin detail criteria and user register.
- Contributed to <u>miLab</u> to develop edit profiles and enhance dashboard UI.

PT BEJANA INVESTIDATA GLOBALINDO - INTERNSHIP FULL STACK DEVELOPER

D.I. Yogyakarta, Indonesia January 2024 - June 2024

- Developed a real-time chat application using Socket.io, integrated with PostgreSQL for data management, and built with Next.js for server-side rendering.
- Contributed to <u>Re-engineering of the Info Pangan Jakarta</u> Admin and User interfaces using Next.js, Vite.js, Chakra UI, and React Query.
- Contributed bug fixing to Biofarma on Electronic Case Report Form (eCRF) to fix status tasks using .NET.
- Contributed to develop export rekening on <u>Adaro Water Solution</u> using React.

INFINITE LEARNING INDONESIA - INDEPENDENT STUDY WEB DEVELOPER

Batam, Riau, Indonesia August 2023 - Dec 2023

- Develop websites including React.js for developing interactive user interfaces, Express.js, and MySQL for creating RESTful API.
- Explored UI/UX design principles, including wireframing, prototyping, and usability testing.
- Applied learned skills through multiple projects, collaborating in team-based environments using Agile methodologies.

HONORS & AWARD

Best Performance of Hack4ID: Green Tech (Jawa Timur) - 1000 Startup Digital

July 2023

Kick-Off & Scouting & Day 1 #Hack4ID: Green Tech (Jawa Timur)

MAHATI ADMIN & MOBILE

January 2024 - Present

Mahati is Mobile Aplikasi Sahabat Hipertensi

- Contributed developing mobile app using Flutter and GetX and consuming backend service with http.
- Develop a full function admin website with Next.js and Shadon UI.
- Contribute refactor and develop backend using Express.js using MySQL and deployed in Docker Portainer.

Tech Stack: Next.js, TailwindCSS, Shaden UI, Express.js, Prisma ORM, MySQL.

SMART RECYCLING Nov 2023 - Dec 2023

Massive Project for Infinite Learning final project.

- Implement full function of backend service using Express JS. Such as auth, event, transaction, and item modules.
- Implement frontend using vite.js and using react toolkit query to manage the API's request. Such as auth, event, transaction, item, and admin page for monitoring data.

Tech Stack: Express, js MySQL, Ant Design, Jest, Docker, Vite. js, Redux. js.

GREEN SAVER Sep 2023 - Oct 2023

Macro Project at Infinite Learning.

- Implements front-end for MVP products such as auth, home, about, contact us and detail news pages.
- Contributed to High Fidelity design on website.

Tech Stack: Next.js, TailwindCSS.

<u>PUFFER</u> Aug 2023 - Sep 2023

Micro Project at Infinite Learning.

- Develop a Low Fidelity, High Fidelity, and Prototype using Figma.
- Contributed to a big idea of the project.

Tech Stack: Figma.

ANIME WATCH WEB Jan 2023 - Mar 2023

Side Project Anime Watch List.

- Develop frontend with Reduxis to manage state API.
- Building Continuous Integration with GitHub Action and Cron Job.
- Develop backend with Nex.js API

Tech Stack: Figma.

SKILLS & TECH STACK

Design Tool: Figma.

Mobile Development: Flutter, Kotlin.

Frontend: Next.js, React.js, Vue.js, Astro.js, Taiwindcss, React Query, Shadon UI, Redux Toolkit.

Backend: Express.js, Prisma ORM, Sequelize ORM, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Elysia.js.

DevOps: Jenkins, Docker, GitHub, GitLab, RabbitMQ.